fatbraintoys.com 2016-10-18

# Fat Brain Toys Privacy Policy

## Updated 9/23/2016

At Fat Brain Toys, your privacy and security are our number one priority. This Privacy Policy was created to inform you of the steps we take to maintain your privacy but also provide you with information on why we gather information from you, how we collect it, how we use it, and the choices you have regarding our use of personal information you have provided. 

By visiting our website or using Fat Brain Toys, you are accepting the terms described in this policy. We may modify or add to this policy on occasion, so we encourage you to review it periodically for updates. 

**Why do we gather information?** Fat Brain Toys gathers personal information to process your orders, help improve our products and customer service, communicate with you, provide a more personalized shopping experience and to inform you, and your gift recipients, of special offers and discounts directly from us, our affiliated brands and selected third parties. 

**Information You Provide.** Fat Brain Toys collects and stores information from you through our website, emails, mail, and telephone. You provide us with your name, address, phone number, email address, credit card information and other information when you do such things as place an order, enter a contest, sign up for promotional emails, request a catalog or make use of other aspects of our website. That information is used to communicate with you, process your order, administer contests, provide catalogs or provide other information that you may request, collect payment for products and services you purchase, respond to your questions, and customize your shopping experience. We may also use this information to send you information about other products and services that may be of interest to you. 

**Credit Card and Personal Information Data.** Fat Brain Toys takes numerous steps to protect any sensitive data you share with us. Fat Brain Toys' website employs Secure Socket Layer (SSL) software which means all personal data you send us (name, address, credit card information, etc.) is encrypted during the entire transmission process, protecting your confidential information from interception and hacking. If you're uncomfortable entering your payment information online, we encourage you to call our customer care representatives at 1-800-590-5987 and they will assist you with your order. 

**PCI Compliance.** Security of your credit card and other payment information is extremely important to us. We meet or exceed all requirements of the Payment Card Industry Data Security Standards (PCI DSS) as established by the PCI Security Standards Council to protect your cardholder data. We employ a variety of methods, including firewalls, encryption, and other best practices to keep your payment information secure at all times. 

**Use of "Cookies" and "Action Tags".** A "cookie" is a small data file sent to your browser from a web server and stored on your computer. We use cookies to let us know that you are a prior customer, user or Member and to provide certain features to you. Most web browsers allow you to disable the use of cookies. However, if you disable this feature, certain aspects of the Fat Brain Toys website, such as the shopping cart, may not function properly. 

We have relationships with third parties who may receive non-personal information directly from the cookies placed by our website on your computer to assist us in analyzing and improving our business and products. Third party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on a user's prior visits to our website. Users may opt out of Google's use of cookies by visiting the Google advertising opt-out page: <http://www.google.com/policies/technologies/ads/>

Our website also uses a common web technology called "action tags" (also called single pixel gifs or web beacons) to anonymously track purchase, usage and other web activity information. Action tags (including third party tags) may be used to provide data to third parties for tracking purposes. However, our website does NOT use action tags to collect or transfer personal information. 

**Email Addresses.** We do not sell or rent our customers' email addresses to third parties (with the exception of the Norton Shopping Guarantee noted below), but we may use these addresses for our own marketing purposes. You can opt out of receiving promotional emails at anytime. Instructions on how to opt out are included in every promotional email or you may opt out here: https://www.fatbraintoys.com/optout.cfm

**Norton Shopping Guarantee.** The Norton Shopping Guarantee is a free service that we provide from the security experts at Symantec to our customers to protect their purchase and protect them against identify fraud. In order for us to activate our customers for this no cost, no obligation program, we provide Symantec with your email address upon making a purchase. You will receive one email from Symantec detailing the benefits of this program. Complete details on this program can be found here: <https://www.nortonshoppingguarantee.com/shoppers/>

**Mailing Addresses.** Your mailing address may be added to our direct mail catalog mailing list. From time to time, that mailing list may be shared, rented or exchanged with other responsible businesses. If you do not want your name shared with businesses not directly affiliated with Fat Brain Toys, or if you do not want to receive the Fat Brain Toys catalog, please call 1-800-590-5987 or email cs@fatbraintoys.com. Please allow 2-4 weeks to process your request. 

**Passwords.** Portions of the website (such as our Member registration) may require registration and log-in processes in which you will select a user ID and password. You are responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of any password and for all activities that occur using your password, whether or not authorized by you. You agree to immediately notify us of any unauthorized use of your password or accounts. 

**Sharing Information.** Unless otherwise noted above, we do not rent, share or exchange customer email addresses in the ordinary course of business. However, we may sell, transfer or assign customer information in connection with a merger, consolidation, sale of assets or similar business transaction. 

**Children.** Although we sell products intended for use by children, those products are intended for purchase by adults only. If you are under 18, you may use FatBrainToys.com only with permission of or supervision by a parent or guardian. The Fat Brain Toys website does not knowingly collect, maintain or disclose personal information from or about children. 

**Contact Information**

Fat Brain Toys  
201516 Nicholas Circle  
Elkhorn, NE 68022  
Phone: 402-779-3181  
Fax: 402-779-3253  
Email: cs@fatbraintoys.com 

If you feel that we are not following our stated Privacy Policy, you may contact us via any of the methods listed above, or state and local chapters of the Better Business Bureau.
